<Document>
  ## 1: Admin Conduct
  - Admins may not handle rulings on any situations that they are directly or indirectly involved with.
  - Admins actions must have irrefutable evidence of rulebreaks (logs, reports, observation).
  - Admin conduct must remain professional in all official player and staff interactions.
  - Punishment will be objective, and take into direct account a note history, or situational circumstances.
  - Powers may not be used to harass or target any specific player.

  ## 2: Ingame Conduct
  - While playing, admins are to be deadminned, unless there are no active admins on, and the adminrelay has remained unanswered for more than ten minutes.
  - Once you have handled an ahelp, respond to the ahelp just so we know someone has handled it.
  - Admins must handle rulebreaks impartially and consistently according to our punishment guideline.
  - Admins must not use their abilities for personal advantage or influence a round in their favour.
  - Not all ahelps concerning other players require resolution, sometimes just looking over the situation is ok.
  - Once you have responded to an ahelp, another admin may not interject until specifically requested to.
  - You may respond to admin issues raised in voice chat with in-game action, however you must request the person in voice chat sends an ahelp regarding the issue, to provide documentation.

  ## 3: Events
  - Players are to all be treated as equal participants and all given opportunity to participate in events.
  - Events must not be used to bruteforce narratives, and are to move with the way players are handling them.
  - Central Command visits are to be exeptional, when faxed and requested to solve issues, and not done without valid IC reason.
  - You may engage in admemes that do not impact rounds to improve player experience.
  - If you believe an admeme may impact the outcome of a round, do a vote beforehand to assess players wiliness to engage.
  - Events must be well structured, or have a narrative purpose, even if it isn't a super serious narrative, it must have a story or goal.
  - If you are seeking to do larger admemes, you may post an event in the discord and make the server aware of it at least three days in advance

  ## 4: Notes
  - Notes are to be used to note player behaviour and are not inherently punishment.
  - Notes may be adjusted upon moderator discussion or appeal, and the player may be informed afterwards.
  - Notes are permanent and may not be removed without appeal.

  ## 5: Confidentiality Disclosure
  - All chats and channels Admins have access to are to remain strictly confidential (discussion, data, investigations, ahelps).
  - Any leakage of these chats is a zero tolerance, and lead to an investigation and immediate dismissal.
  - When adminned you are to disable subtle chat.
</Document>
