<Document>
  # Community Rules

  These are our Community rules, breaking these will result in a community wide punishment (Discord and game server) punishment.

  - You must be 18 or older to be part of this community.
  - Be polite, civil and respectful towards others.
  - Hate speech in any form is forbidden (including ic speciesm, racism etc)
  - No political, religious, or other controversial topics.
  - No Advertising or Self-Promotion.
  - Speak English.

  # Admin Rules
  In addition to these rules admins must also follow the [textlink="admin rules" link="FloofAdminRules"].

  # Game Server Rules

  ## 0: Implicit rules
  - 0.1 Admins have the final say on rulings, as well as the ability to make calls to preserve the players both in and out of game, and may ban or kick accordingly to keep everyone safe and happy.
  - 0.2 There will be NSFW content in this server, you will engage with it if you join. If you are uncomfortable with it, do not connect.

  ## Section 1: Out Of Character
  - 1.1 Be polite, civil and respectful towards other players and admins.
  - 1.2 Hate speech in any form is forbidden (including ic speciesm, racism etc)
  - 1.3 Do not disconnect during an AHelp in progress (if connection is lost due to Internet issues, open a ticket on the Discord ASAP).
  - 1.4 It is forbidden to livestream rounds to others or share recorded gameplay outside of Euphoria Station without consent of all parties involved.
  - 1.5 Spying on other people's personal activities (especially ERP) is not permitted.
  - 1.6 Do not spam, or advertise without approval.
  - 1.7 No rules lawyering.
  - 1.8 Don't violently impede evac.

  ## Section 2: Consent
  - 2.1 Both roleplay and ERP require all players involved to be consenting. If your consent is not respected, immediately AHelp or open a ticket.
  - 2.2 Roleplay may occur under implied consent when all players involved engage in roleplay that suggests mutual willingness with no OOC objections raised during or immediately after the interaction.
  - 2.3 It is your responsibility to keep your consent preferences up to date.
  - 2.4 While usage of kinks or sex mechanics for gameplay or non-sexual roleplay purposes is not forbidden per se, you must seek consent from everybody who could be exposed to it.

  ## 3: Roleplay & Characters
  - 3.1 You are a reasonable, sane person capable of independent survival.
  - 3.2 Regardless of the method of your species' reproduction or proliferation, your character is at least 18 years of age.
  - 3.3 While a non-antagonist you are crew aligned, and should not assist antagonists in destruction or lawbreaking.
  - 3.4 You are capable of remembering past rounds, but may not hold those actions as grudges against someone.
  - 3.5 You may not roleplay suicidal topics.

  ## 4: Powergaming
  - 4.1 Do not use metacommunications to gain an ingame advantage
  - 4.2 Do not use cheats, exploits or unintended game mechanics,
  - 4.3 Do not metagame or metagrudge

  ## 5: Death & New Life
  - 5.1 Characters maintain all memory up until death.
  - 5.2 Upon death, characters lose all memories five minutes prior to dying.
  - 5.3 Characters’ perception during a critical state is impaired (no distinct names, faces, objects, locations).
  - 5.4 If a player is brought back to life by means of cloning, they lose all the memories that have been acquired so far into shift.
  - 5.5 If your character dies or enters cryostasis beyond the point of no return, you normally cannot respawn as the same character. Seek permission from an admin if you need or wish to do so.

  ## 6: Erotic-Role-Play (ERP) and NSFW
  - 6.1 Do not kinkshame.
  - 6.2 All underage and ageplay content is forbidden.
  - 6.3 You may not ERP with an entity that cannot verbally consent to a sexual interaction.
  - 6.4 Roleplay of controversial, heavy themes and topics that would make most people uncomfortable (extreme topics) must be kept out of the public eye and ear and make use of subtle verbs (subtle emote, subtle LOOC, and whisper). If you encounter an extreme topic do not engage with it at all IC, immediately ahelp.
  - 6.5 Active ERP must make use of subtle verbs (subtle emote, subtle LOOC, and whisper).
  - 6.6 Public ERP is allowed, if it is explicitly marked, and not involving extreme themes, players may use regular emotes here, it is up to other players to move away from these areas if they are made uncomfortable.
  - 6.7 Do not use ERP as bait for kill objectives, unless done with OOC consent of all parties involved.
  - 6.8 Your job comes before ERP, if required you must stop a scene to do your duty. Select passenger if you wish to ERP in peace.
  - 6.9 Nice.
  - 6.10 Do not abuse your position of power (unless this is being done privately and with consent of all parties involved).

  ## 7: Command and security
  - 7.1 While an antagonist, do not cause unnecessary destruction or death outside the scope of your objectives.
  - 7.2 Command and security are held to a higher standard of roleplay, and are expected to follow reasonable escalation.
</Document>
